[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The four Jovian planets in the Solar system are Jupiter, Saturn, Neptune and which other planet?", "correct_answer": "Uranus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Venus", "Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous person, who received the Kennedy Center Honors in 2000, was born in St. Louis, Missouri?", "correct_answer": "Chuck Berry", "incorrect_answers": ["Thurgood Marshall", "Harry S. Truman", "Bo Didley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During their lightsaber duel, what does Darth Vader tell Luke Skywalker?", "correct_answer": "Luke is his son", "incorrect_answers": ["He will kill him", "Leia was killed", "The Rebellion is over"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character played by Dax Shepard in the comedy film Idiocracy?", "correct_answer": "Frito", "incorrect_answers": ["Doctor", "Joe", "Prosecutor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not an original member of The Mamas  the Papas?", "correct_answer": "Jill Gibson", "incorrect_answers": ["John Phillips", "Denny Doherty", "Cass Elliot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is not a shade of purple?", "correct_answer": "Vermilion", "incorrect_answers": ["Heliotrope", "Mountbatten pink", "Thistle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the two famous streets that were the heart of the hippie movement.", "correct_answer": "Haight and Ashbury", "incorrect_answers": ["Hollywood and Vine", "Times Square and 42nd Street", "Washington Square and Alphabet City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress first crossed the screen in a remake of The Parent Trap. In Mean Girls, she played the new student, Cady Heron.", "correct_answer": "Lindsay Lohan", "incorrect_answers": ["Mischa Barton", "Hilary Duff", "Miley Cyrus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the dramedy Little Miss Sunshine, what is the major problem of Grandpa, played by Alan Arkin?", "correct_answer": "Heroin addiction", "incorrect_answers": ["Hes a drunk.", "His granddaughter does not  love him.", "He wants to live with his love interest, played by  Alicia Forbes."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which animal group is also a collective name for software errors?", "correct_answer": "Bugs", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "Spiders", "Ants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Aliens, what did Cpl. Hicks keep handy for close encounters?", "correct_answer": "Shotgun", "incorrect_answers": ["Knife", "Breath Mints", "Cologne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following characters made their debut in Old Possums Book of Practical Cats?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Rumpleteazer", "Old Deuteronomy", "The Rum Tum Tiger"]}]